AMRIZ JANTAN Full-Stack Developer

SUMMARY

Certified Full Stack Developer with analytical and creative skills in addition to strong entrepreneurship. Multidisciplinary background with 7+ years experience in business development that includes both retail and digital operations as Co-founder of a Japanese lifestyle store and fashion label. Highly skilled in complex risk assessment and key corporate client advisory with 9+ years experience in the corporate environment as a Senior Risk Analyst.

SKILLS / TECHNOLOGIES

HTML / CSS

Javascript

Angular

React

REST API

MongoDB

NODE.js

AWS

Bootstrap

Wordpress

LANGUAGES

English – Advanced German – Advanced Bahasa Malaysia – Native Japanese - Basic

PROJECTS

Developed a single page, responsive movie database web application that includes several interface views that will handle data through the previously-defined REST API endpoints using MEAN stack.

CONTACT

GitHub: github.com/amrizjantan

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/amriz-jantan Portfolio: amrizjantan.github.io/Portfolio-

Revamp

Phone: +49 (0)176 3228 2463 Email: amrizjantan@gmail.com Address: Hamburg, Germany.

Open to remote roles.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Developer, Freelance

Hamburg and Berlin Germany, 2021 to present

 Designed, developed and maintained an on-line shop www.bluesleeve.de with Wordpress technology that successfully digitalized the business operation, increased sales and customer awareness.

Co-Founder, Bluesleeve Japanese lifestyle Store

Hamburg Germany, 2014 to present

- Assumed full responsibility in creating business modules, plans and goals that ensured maximum profits and return on investment.
- Oversaw all aspects of business development, daily retail and online activities which maintained effective and smooth business operations.
- Collaborated and coordinated with artists, designers and partners on art exhibitions and business projects that increased shop's reputation and products diversity.
- Ensured timely preparation of business accounting and tax submission resulted to stable cash flow management and regulator's compliance.
- Offered professional advise and shopping experience in order to maintain customer satisfaction and retention.

Risk Analyst, AON Corporation

Hamburg Germany, 2008 to 2013

- Analysed client's complex risk portfolio to identify and measure political, management, financial and non-financial exposures to possible loss prior to designing a comprehensive Risk Management.
- Advised key corporate clients on risk policies and processes in accordance to the designed framework that ensured successful risk mitigation and business contingency.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development Program

CareerFoundry, Berlin Germany, 2022

- Intensive 7 months training focused on developing a fluency in JavaScript, Node.js, React, HTML5, and CSS3.
- Built multiple projects from scratch using HTML5, CSS3, Heroku, MEAN and MERN stacks.
- Implemented user authentication and authorization using AWS, conducted unit and functional tests using Jest, Cucumber, and Puppeteer, and created user stories on Kanban boards following Agile processes.
- Learned the value of version control while using Git and GitHub.

Bachelors Degree, Risk Management

MARA University of Technology, Kuala Lumpur Malaysia, 2002